{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420609234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420609234"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 274762ce-cf5f-43ca-94ac-48b43c6dd385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420614960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420614960"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 274762ce-cf5f-43ca-94ac-48b43c6dd385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420647478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420647478"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 274762ce-cf5f-43ca-94ac-48b43c6dd385"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_num.0..9.GL_SD_OFFW1_M.bub3.15"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-2-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420647545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420647544"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" cfa2d88a-c2b6-4ccd-93e4-7583e80e0846"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_18"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Msitu huo ulikuwa na majitu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAJITU"," userResponse":" MAJITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420657428","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420657428"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420659637","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420659636"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" omba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBA"," userResponse":" OMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420661216","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420661215"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420663701","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420663701"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ovaroli"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OVAROLI"," userResponse":" OVAROLI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420665270","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420665270"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" ONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420668793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420668793"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ona"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ONA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420670381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420670380"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" OA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420674003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420674003"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" oa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420675592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420675592"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-O.rand.54__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420684961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420684961"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420685035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420685035"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 71a9462d-65c2-43db-9edf-24809215ed5b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-O.rand.54__it_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ofisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OFISI"," userResponse":" OFISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420696114","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420696114"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420699840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420699840"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420704002","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420704002"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420705771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420705770"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_1v7"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420709249","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420709249"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420711189","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420711189"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_2v7"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420715079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420715079"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420717599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420717599"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_3v9"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420722086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420722086"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420726479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420726479"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v1"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420731522","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420731522"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_4v5"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420735394","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420735393"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420743829","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420743829"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420753718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420753718"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_8v5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420759163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420759162"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" workedExample"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420761126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420761125"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 9fc07e59-0356-4ebf-a11c-868f62c5ec68"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" numdiscr"," tutorId":" numcompare_1d__it_5"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" ND_7v5"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420770849","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420770849"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420771595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420771594"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420772430","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420772430"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420773317","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420773316"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420773918","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420773918"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420774677","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420774676"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo a a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420777163","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420777163"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420777675","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420777675"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420778532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420778531"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420779495","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420779494"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420780056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420780056"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420780774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420780773"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama embe a a a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420783680","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420783679"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420784410","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420784409"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420784527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420784527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420785954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420785954"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420786347","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420786346"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420786384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420786384"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo e e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420790113","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420790113"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420790775","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420790775"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420791699","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420791699"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420792585","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420792585"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420792817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420792816"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420792854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420792854"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina mkia chini e e e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420797096","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420797095"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420797721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420797721"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420797805","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420797805"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420798600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420798600"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420799527","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420799527"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420800763","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420800763"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo i i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420802908","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420802907"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INA"," userResponse":" INA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420803613","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420803612"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOFIA"," userResponse":" KOFIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420803883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420803883"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420804965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420804965"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420805515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420805514"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420805563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420805563"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ina kofia juu i i i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420810012","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420810011"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420810621","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420810620"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420811433","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420811433"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420811567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420811567"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420812322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420812321"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420813645","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420813644"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo o o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420816027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420816027"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420816529","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420816529"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420817545","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420817545"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPIRA"," userResponse":" MPIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420818420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420818420"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420819027","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420819026"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420819820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420819819"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama mpira o o o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420822872","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420822872"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420824847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420824846"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIYO"," userResponse":" NDIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420825100","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420825100"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420825493","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420825492"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420825706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420825705"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420826608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420826607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hiyo ndiyo u u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420829361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420829361"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKO"," userResponse":" IKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420829830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420829830"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420830837","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420830836"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420831037","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420831036"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420832305","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420832304"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420833121","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420833120"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420835673","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420835672"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420835771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420835771"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" e4d4b893-1b95-411c-9664-acf425bfcd00"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_2__it_4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Iko kama kikombe u u u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420884192","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420884192"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_chekechea-ndoto-refu-mbegu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" refu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420887662","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420887662"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_chekechea-ndoto-refu-mbegu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" mbegu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420890329","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420890329"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_chekechea-ndoto-refu-mbegu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" ndoto"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420893028","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420893028"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_chekechea-ndoto-refu-mbegu"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420934102","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420934102"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" huzuni_dhoruba-huzuni-chiriku-wazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" huzuni"," userResponse":" huzuni"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420962048","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420962048"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_ngozi-yuko-mali-chekechea"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548420983891","data":{"timestamp":" 1548420983891"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chekechea_pango-mifugo-chekechea-samahani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chekechea"," userResponse":" chekechea"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421013863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421013863"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kubwa_kubwa-nyingine-hadi-tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kubwa"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421017283","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421017282"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kubwa_kubwa-nyingine-hadi-tafadhali"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" kubwa"," userResponse":" kubwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421045406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421045406"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chupa_chupa-mashamba-mdomo-adhabu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" chupa"," userResponse":" chupa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421093634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421093634"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mahali_maisha-mbali-mahali-nyumba"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" mahali"," userResponse":" mahali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421116607","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421116607"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ambia_Ambia-ambamo-makofi-endelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" Ambia"," userResponse":" Ambia"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421153743","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421153743"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" cloze"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ambia_Ambia-ambamo-makofi-endelea"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421153850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421153850"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHACHE"," userResponse":" CHACHE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:O..O.vow.rand.all.stat.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421159575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421159575"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"numcompare:1d__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548421165185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548421165184"," userId":" 6116002649"," sessionId":" 6116002649_20190125_154942"," gameId":" 3f4aaec3-7e0f-420c-be89-ef8a693ea6eb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_16"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Walikuwa wamezaliwa saa chache tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}